<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wildlife</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <!--login related-->
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Register</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="minimum_password">Password too short, enter minimum 6 characters!</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed, check your email and password or sign up</string>
    <string name="change_email">Change Email</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="send_password_reset_email">Send Password reset email</string>
    <string name="remove_user">Remove user</string>
    <string name="new_pass">New Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Firebase</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Get registered in Firebase now!</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registered. Login Me!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reset_password">ResetPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="btn_forgot_password">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="btn_reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="btn_back"><![CDATA[<< Back]]></string>
    <string name="hint_new_email">New Email</string>
    <string name="btn_change">Change</string>
    <string name="btn_send">Send</string>
    <string name="btn_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="lbl_forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_msg">We just need your registered Email Id to sent you password reset instructions.</string>

    <!--end of login related-->

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_crime">Add Crime</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page">Home</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "\n\nSAVE OUR BELOVED WILDLIFE CREATURES\n\n"
        "Wildlife traditionally refers to undomesticated animal species, but has come to include all"
        "plants, fungi, and other organisms that grow or live wild in an area without being introduced"
        "by humans. Deserts, forests, rain forests, plains, grasslands and other areas including the"
        "most developed urban areas, all have distinct forms of wildlife.\n"
        "In more than 50 years of conservation, we have never seen wildlife crime on such a scale."
        "Wildlife crime is now the most urgent threat to three of the world's best-loved species—elephants,"
        "rhinos and tigers.\n\n"
        "Illegal wildlife trade has exploded to meet increasing demand for elephant ivory, rhino horns,"
        "and tiger products, particularly in Asia. Controlled by dangerous crime syndicates, wildlife is "
        "trafficked much like drugs or weapons. Wildlife criminals often operate with impunity, making "
        "the trade a low-risk/high-profit business.\n\n"
        "Our application is to help the wildlife animals to get their rights and live in peace."
        "You just have to report anything wrong thing you see in the wildlife environment."
"Speak up on behalf of those on the frontlines being threatened by armed poachers so they are properly "
        "equipped, trained and compensated. The wildlife officer will look after your report and take action"
        "according to the laws.\n\n\n"
"YOU CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE"
    </string>
    <string name="app_help">
        "\nSteps to save India's diverse wildlife:"
"\n\n\nStep 1: Sign up to add crime"
"\n\nStep 2: Open add crime page and fill out the details asked about the crime."
"\n\nStep 2(a): If you do not know the name of the species then check the reference section and fill the details."
"\n\nStep 2(b): Save the crime"
"\n\nStep 3: You can view and edit your added crimes using view reports."
"\n\nStep 4: Your can view all the crimes till date in view crime section."
"\n\nStep 5: Logout"
"\n\n\nTHANK YOU FOR CONTRIBUTING TO SAVE INDIA'S DIVERSE WILDLIFE"
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_signup">SignupActivity</string>
</resources>
